https://granitesafes.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Welcome to Granite Safes
Products search
My Account
My Basket (0)
Skip to content
MENUMENUHomeSafes
Home SafesOffice SafesBudget SafesAiS Insurance Approved SafesLaptop SafesDeposit SafesHotel SafesUnderfloor SafesWall Safes
Fire Safes
View All Fire SafesFire Filing Drawers & CabinetsChurch SafesDocument Fire SafesDigital Media Fire SafesData Fire Safes
Key Security
Deep Key SafesHigh Security Key SafesKey Deposit CabinetsSpecialist Keys Systems
Secure Storage
Exam Paper CabinetsSecurity CabinetsMedical StorageGun Cabinets
Shop By Cash Cover
Cash £1,000/ £10,000 ValuablesCash £1,500/ £15,000 ValuablesCash £2,000/ £20,000 ValuablesCash £2,500/ £25,000 ValuablesCash £3,000/ £30,000 ValuablesCash £3,500/ £35,000 ValuablesCash £4,000/ £40,000 Valuables
Eurograde Safes
Euro Grade 0Euro Grade 1Euro Grade 2Euro Grade 3Euro Grade 4Euro Grade 5Euro Grade 6
Brands
View All BrandsSMP Security SafesChubbsafesPhoenix SafesSecurikeyChurchill Safes
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand what information may be gathered from you and how we will use it.  Any personal information that you provide to us will only be used in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy; therefore please read it and our Terms of Use carefully before using our site.  By accessing and using our site, you agree to be bound by them and to abide by them.  If you do not agree to be bound in this way, do not continue to access or use our site.  Unless the context requires otherwise, terms used in this Privacy Policy shall be as defined in our Terms of Use.1.             Introduction1.1          This Privacy Policy does not apply to any content or information contained in or collected from or submitted to any third party sites that you access via any link from our site and we do not accept any liability for such third party sites.1.2          For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), Associated Safe Systems Limited t/a Granite Safes is the data controller.1.3          Our nominated representative for the purpose of the Act is Melissa Barnett.2.             What Personal Information do We Collect?  We may collect and process the following personal information about you:2.1          If you make an enquiry with us or request a quotation or other contact from us, we may:2.1.1       store your name, geographical address and postcode, email address and phone numbers in order to communicate with you;2.1.2       keep a record of any such correspondence;2.1.3       store information about your preferences regarding our goods and/or services and whether and by which method you wish to be contacted by us or third parties for marketing purposes.2.2          If you register to use our site or open an account on our site, we may store:2.2.1       your name, geographical address and postcode, your email address and contact phone numbers in order to communicate with you;2.2.2       your user identification code, user name, password and any other memorable information you provide to us in order to remind you of the same or reactivate your account.2.3          If you order goods and /or services from our site, we may:2.3.1       store your name, geographical address and postcode, your email address and contact phone numbers in order to communicate with you and inform you of the status and progress of your order;2.3.2       store any delivery address (where this is different to your geographical address);2.3.3       store your order details, and delivery status to fulfil our contract with you2.3.4       or our nominated providers of payment services may, collect your payment details, however we will not store such details.2.4          We may from time to time store details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.2.5          We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.2.6          We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer financial details with any 3rd parties3.             How We Use Your Information3.1          The information we hold about you may be used in the following ways:3.1.1       to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;3.1.2       to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;3.1.3       to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;3.1.4       to notify you about changes to our service;3.1.5       to contact you by post, email telephone, SMS and/or MMS to inform you:(i)             of other products and/or services we supply which may interest you;(ii)            of products and/or services for other companies within our group, which may interest you;(iii)           of products and/or services from third parties which may interest you;where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes at the relevant time you provide such information to us.4.             Disclosure of Your Information4.1          We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.4.2          We may disclose your personal information to third parties in the following circumstances:4.2.1       if we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;4.2.2       if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;4.2.3       if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or Terms and Conditions of Supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Associated Safe Systems Limited t/a Granite Safes, our group companies, customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.5.             Storage of Your Personal Information5.1          The personal information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.  By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.   We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.5.2          All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be processed either by PayPal in accordance with PayPal’s standard terms and conditions (visit Paypal) or Sage Pay in accordance with Sage Pay’s standard terms and conditions (visit Sagepay) depending on which method of payment is chosen by you.5.3          Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.6.             CookiesOur site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy.7.             Your Rights7.1          You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by ticking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at sales@granitesafes.co.uk.7.2          Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.8.             Updates and ChangesWe may update and/or change this Privacy Policy at any time by amending this page.  Any such updates and/or changes are effective immediately from the time they are included on our site.  Therefore you agree to review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are or become aware of any such updates and/or changes.  If you do not wish to accept the new Privacy Policy, you should not continue to use our site.  If you continue to use our site after the date the updates and/or changes come into effect, your use of our site indicates your agreement to be bound by the new Privacy Policy.9.             Data Protection ActThe Act gives you the right to access information held about you. You can request a copy of such information by emailing sales@granitesafes.co.uk.  Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.10.          Your ConcernsIf you have any questions, comments, requests or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact sales@granitesafes.co.uk. COOKIE REFERENCEMagento Standard CookiesCookie NameCookie DescriptionUSER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIEIndicates if a customer is allowed to use cookies.external_no_cacheA flag that indicates if caching is disabled.persistent_shopping_cartThe session key.StfIf product links were sent to friends, stores the timestamps in the format: $timeStamp1, $timestamp2, …, $timestampN.pollNA poll ID that indicates if a vote has occurred.frontendSession IDguest-viewAllows guests to edit their orders.Google Analytics CookiesJavaScript Library: ga.jsCookieDescription__utmaDistinguishes shoppers and sessions .This cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes and there is no existing __utma cookie. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.__utmtUsed to throttle request rate.__utmbDetermines new sessions/visits. This cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes and there is no existing __utmb cookie. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics._utmzSaves the traffic source or campaign that explains how the shopper reached your site. The cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes, and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.__utmvStores visitor-level custom variable data. This cookie is created when a developer uses the _setCustomVar method with a visitor-level custom variable. This cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Quick LinksHomepage
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
My account
Shop
Coronavirus Statement
Social
Newsletter
0161 819 6883
© Copyright 2020 Granite Safes. Part of the Safe Systems Group
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
